Hello Hello friend welcome to Aptitude Test,
in today's video we are going to see
how to renew account on Adi,
if your account has been opened on it
or is about to be opened then it is a very
simple step, you can renew it
and if you have not subscribed to the channel till now
then subscribe to this channel,
click on the bell icon so that you keep getting
new updates, so let's start
somehow
[Music]
so friends if you have an Idea account
then there is a prepaid account on it as well, so as a sample
I have made some points here,
according to this point we will see
if your account is of 5 years and you have to deposit
₹1000 every month and accordingly
you will also get interest here, this
interest rate will keep changing according to the role of post office,
it is not thick,
after that let's see that we have done ₹100 for 5 years, so
our motor is educated, it happens at that
time and plus job
interview mote, that too will
come here in advocates  Friends, after that let's talk about the
expiry date, even if
your VAT has expired, then
you don't have to pay the amount you are going to get here,
after that what you have to do is
submit an application here, so you
can see here that
I have made a sample application and here we have
written the post master's
name in the application, so you can do it, below that
enter your post office address and your pin code here below,
after that friends you can see that you can
also enter the subject here, so now see,
here in the subject we are giving the
application for RD account from the center's RD account,
below that write Nice
Picture Sir Plus I and below it
your name will appear, whatever your name is, you
enter it here, I have left a line space,
after that it is written here that you have an
RD account which you have
opened in front of their post office and friends
enter the name here, after that
you have to enter your Idea number here also
and its corresponding date is the tweet and
your expiry  You have to enter the date here as well,
after that you have to write a simple salutation
that they want to review by RD account, that is,
after half an hour you have to
select yours here, after that thanks and
record, enter your name, your place and mobile
number here, so friends, it is over to
submit this application,
before that you should know one important thing that
if your account is ace
then you do not have to withdraw its amount,
if you withdraw the amount
then you can keep your RD account here,
if you have
withdrawn from us then you will have to
open a new account, you cannot keep it running,
after that friends, if
you renew your account then
whatever amount you have deposited in the last 5
years with the wish plus interest, if it is
more than, for example, if the
management has taken it from this, then
after your renewal, among these
roles in it, you will get its interface here, that is, as if
we open this account then
Its entry starts from zero
and every month we keep
adding Tarzan Rupees in it and then whatever the total
amount is, friend, I
get its interest here but
friends if we invest half an hour then
you can see here that it is 7000
plus we will get its interest, so
as we keep adding amount in it every month,
we will keep getting the interest of the total arm hole here from the
Interpress Post Office,
this is a very good benefit in this,
despite this if you have any question or any other
question then friends you
can ask us in the comment, so friends if
you liked this information like the video,
subscribe to the channel and
click on the bell icon so that we keep making such new
videos and you keep getting updates,
thank you and
show more